export default [
    {
        question: 'React is _______',
        answers: [
            'Module based',
            'Component based',
            'Both of above',
            'None of above'
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'As soon as the state of react component is changed, component will',
        answers: [
            'Does nothing , you have to call render method to render the component again',
            'be created again from scratch',
            're-renders the component',
            'None of above'
        ],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'We can go for ______ when there is possibility that our user could change the data?',
        answers: [
            'Keys',
            'Ref',
            'Both',
            'None of above'
        ],
        correct: 1
    },

    {
        question: 'JSX is typesafe?',
        answers: [
            'True',
            'False',
            'None of the Above',
            'Cannot Be Determined'
        ],
        correct: 1
    },    
    {
        question: 'Keys are given to a list of elements in react. These keys should be -',
        answers: [
            'Do not requires to be unique',
            'Unique in the DOM', 
            'Unique among the siblings only', 
            'All of the Above'
        ],    
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'ReactJS uses _____ to increase performance',
        answers: [
            'Original DOM',
            'Virtual DOM', 
            'Both 1 & 2', 
            'None of the above'
        ],    
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'In React what is used to pass data to a component from outside?',
        answers: [
            'setState',
            'render with arguments', 
            'props', 
            'PropTypes'
        ],    
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What is ReactJS?',
        answers: [
            'Server side Framework',
            'A Library for building interaction interfaces', 
            'User-interface framework', 
            'None of the Above'
        ],    
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'State in react is________',
        answers: [
            'Internal storage of the component',
            'A permanent storage',
            'Both of Above', 
            'None of the Above'
        ],    
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Everything in React is a _____________',
        answers: [
            'Module',
            'Component', 
            'Package', 
            'Class'
        ],    
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'React merges the object you provide into the current state using which of the following',
        answers: [
            'setState()',
            'State()', 
            'getState()', 
            'None of the Above'
        ],    
        correct: 1
    },    
    {
        question: 'Arbitrary inputs of components are called?',
        answers: [
            'Keys',
            'Props', 
            'Elements', 
            'Ref'
        ],    
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: '_____ can be done while more than one element needs to be returned from a component?',
        answers: [
            'Abstraction',
            'Packing', 
            'Insulation', 
            'Wrapping'
        ],    
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following needs to be updated to achieve dynamic UI updates?',
        answers: [
            'State',
            'Props', 
            'Components', 
            'None of the Above'
        ],    
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Lifecycle methods are mainly used _____',
        answers: [
            'To keep track of event history',
            'To enhance components', 
            'Free up resources', 
            'None of the Above'
        ],    
        correct: 3
    }
]